Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: General Files, 1944-2000
  - Political Action: Elections II, 1984-1985; cuid5867 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Political Action: Elections III, 1984-1985; cuid5868 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Political Action: Elections IV, 1984-1985, 1992; cuid5869 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Political Action: Elections (Oversize), 1982; cuid5870 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Political Action: Opposition to MVO Contract with Vera Institute of Justice, 1989-1990; cuid5871 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Political Action: Presidential Campaign (Walter Mondale), 1983-1984; cuid5872 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Political Action: Screening Committee, 1980; cuid5873 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Political Action: Screening Committee, 1986; cuid5874 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Professional Division: Leaflets, 1970-1971; cuid5875 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Professional Services: Reports, undated; cuid5876 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Quality of Work Life Program, 1993-1995; cuid5877 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Retirees and Cultural Affairs Department, 1971-1976, 1985-1986; cuid5878 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Safety and Health Unit, 1982; cuid5879 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - School Crossing Guards Organizing Campaign, 1974-1975, 1978-1980; cuid5880 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Shop Stewards Manual, 1964; cuid5881 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Summer Hours Dispute, 1966; cuid5882 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Test Manual, undated; cuid5883 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Test Preparation Course: Supervising Clerk-Stenographer, 1971; cuid5884 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Test Preparation Manual: Supervising Clerk (Income Maintenance), ca.1962; cuid5885 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Publicity, 1961-1962; cuid5886 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - United Federation of Teachers: Strike Clippings, 1967-1968; cuid5887 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Vietnam War, 1970; cuid5888 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Women's Committee, 1982-1984, 1990; cuid5889 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Oversize Materials.
    - NOTE: This box holds oversize materials; individual folders are listed where they would normally appear in the finding-aid., undated; cuid5890 (Box 60)
- Series VI: Restricted Materials, 1967-1997
  Conditions Governing Access
  Materials in this series are closed for privacy reasons and will be opened 50 years after their date of creation.
  - Local 1407 (Accountants, Statisticians, and Actuaries) (Restricted), 1967; cuid5891 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - CETA Questionnaire (Restricted), 1979; cuid5892 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Local 420 Members' Petition (Restricted), 1979; cuid5893 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Bridge and Tunnel Officers Benevolent Association v. Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority (Lukas et al. v. Ascher et al.) (Restricted), 1996; cuid5894 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union, Local 153 (Restricted), 1997; cuid5895 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Series VII: Ken Nash Collection - Audio Reels, 1977-1990
  - Subseries VII:A: "It's Your City, It's Our Job" Radio Show Audio Reels, 1986-1990.
    - Bridges, May 29, [?]; cuid5896 (Box 62, Reel 1)
    - Local 299, Undated; cuid5897 (Box 62, Reel 2)
    - Local 299 Recreation, Jun 25, [?]; cuid5898 (Box 62, Reel 3)
    - [Music and Songs] (Master Copy), Undated; cuid5899 (Box 62, Reel 4)
    - [Unidentified], Nov 15, [?]; cuid5900 (Box 62, Reel 5)
    - [Unidentified], Nov 22, [?]; cuid5901 (Box 62, Reel 6)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Parts I and II, Dec 18, 1986; cuid5902 (Box 62, Reel 7)
    - Women at Work, Mar 5, 1987; cuid5903 (Box 62, Reel 8)
    - New York City Botanical Gardeners, Mar 26, 1987; cuid5904 (Box 62, Reel 9)
    - March on Washington, Apr 9, 1987; cuid5905 (Box 62, Reel 10)
    - Recreation Program, May 7, 1987; cuid5906 (Box 62, Reel 11)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Labor History, May 21, 1987; cuid5907 (Box 63, Reel 12)
    - Safety and Health, Jun 4, 1987; cuid5908 (Box 63, Reel 13)
    - Summer Recreation, Jun 25, 1987; cuid5909 (Box 63, Reel 14)
    - Work With the Homeless, Jul 23, 1987; cuid5910 (Box 63, Reel 15)
    - Emergency Medical Services, Oct 21, 1987; cuid5911 (Box 63, Reel 16)
    - Puerto Rican Heritage Week, Nov 8, 1987; cuid5912 (Box 63, Reel 17)
    - Whistleblowers, Nov 22, 1987; cuid5913 (Box 63, Reel 18)
    - 911 Technicians, Jan 3, 1988; cuid5914 (Box 63, Reel 19)
    - New York Public Health System, Jan 19, 1988; cuid5915 (Box 63, Reel 20)
    - Black History Month, Feb 3, 1988; cuid5916 (Box 63, Reel 21)
    - Black History Month (Working Dub), Feb 24, 1988; cuid5917 (Box 63, Reel 22)
    - Black History Month (Master Copy), Feb 24, 1988; cuid5918 (Box 63, Reel 23)
    - Museums, May 1, 1988; cuid5919 (Box 64, Reel 24)
    - Tax Assessors, May 15, 1988; cuid5920 (Box 64, Reel 25)
    - Museums, Jun 12, 1988; cuid5921 (Box 64, Reel 26)
    - Public Libraries, Jun 26, 1988; cuid5922 (Box 64, Reel 27)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 1 and 2, Jul 10, 1988; cuid5923 (Box 64, Reel 28, Box Shared Tamiment 113)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 3 and 4, Jul 24, 1988 [?]; cuid5924 (Box 64, Reel 29, Box Shared Tamiment 113)
      Scope and Content Note
      For small portion of recording, second audio content at different speed heard under the main content which resulted in a brief decrease in sound quality.
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 5 and 6, Jul 17, 1988 [?]; cuid5925 (Box 64, Reel 30, Box Shared Tamiment 113)
    - New Yorkers at Work, Parts 7 and 8, 1988; cuid5926 (Box 64, Reel 31, Box Shared Tamiment 113)
    - Come to the Cabaret (Dec 23); Hurricane Relief Committees (Jan 6), 1988-1989; cuid5927 (Box 64, Reel 32)
    - [Intro and Closing], Apr 9, 1990; cuid5928 (Box 64, Reel 33)
    - [Intro, Closing, and Promos], Apr 9, 1990; cuid5929 (Box 64, Reel 34)
  - Subseries VII:B: Other DC 37 Audio Reels, 1985-1990.
    - "Negotiation" (Radio Spots featuring Baylin, Riccio, and Mariano), Jan 9, 1985; cuid5930 (Box 65, Reel 35)
    - "Coalition" (Radio Spots featuring Wondolowski, Johnson, Arlene Baylor, and Marco Castro), Jan 15, 1985; cuid5931 (Box 65, Reel 36)
    - "Haven't We Learned Anything from the 70s?" (Speech by Stanley Hill), Oct 1, 1990; cuid5932 (Box 65, Reel 37)
    - "Contract Rally" (Radio Spot by Stanley Hill), Nov 2, 1990; cuid5933 (Box 65, Reel 38)
    - "Just Like You" (Speech by Stanley Hill), Dec 23, 1990; cuid5934 (Box 65, Reel 39)
  - Subseries VII:C: Non-DC 37 Audio Reels, 1977-1980.
    - Crossroads: "Women in China" (NPR Program), Aug 11, 1977; cuid5935 (Box 65, Reel 40)
    - The Mind's Eye: "Cowboy" (NPR Program by Josh Darsa), Oct 4, 1980; cuid5936 (Box 65, Reel 41)
- Series VIII: Ken Nash Collection - Audio Cassettes, 1986-1999
  - Subseries VIII:A: "It's Your City, It's Our Job" Audio Cassettes, 1986-1998.
    - DC37 Theme Song, Undated; cuid5937 (Box 66, Cassette 42)
    - EMS Employees, Undated; cuid5938 (Box 66, Cassette 43)
    - Holiday/Christmas Show, Undated; cuid5939 (Box 66, Cassette 44)
    - Puerto Rico, Undated; cuid5940 (Box 66, Cassette 45)
    - Puerto Rico, Undated; cuid5941 (Box 66, Cassette 46)
    - Puerto Rico, Undated; cuid5942 (Box 66, Cassette 47)
    - Shop Stewards, undated; cuid5943 (Box 67, Cassette 148)
    - Budget Smarts, undated; cuid5944 (Box 67, Cassette 149, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_255)
    - Wurf, Mildred and Elma Osborne, May 26, [?]; cuid5945 (Box 66, Cassette 48)
    - Kids, School, and Drugs, Oct 2, 1986; cuid5946 (Box 66, Cassette 49)
    - Drugs in Schools (part 1), Oct 9, 1986; cuid5947 (Box 66, Cassette 50-53)
    - Drugs in Schools (part 2), Oct 9, 1986; cuid5948 (Box 66, Cassette 54-55)
    - Able But Disabled, Oct 16, 1986; cuid5949 (Box 66, Cassette 56-57)
    - Able But Disabled (part 1), Oct 16, 1986; cuid5950 (Box 66, Cassette 58-62)
    - Able But Disabled (part 2), Oct 16, 1986; cuid5951 (Box 66, Cassette 63-66)
    - Politics and Poker, Oct 30, 1986; cuid5952 (Box 66, Cassette 67)
    - Union Memories, Dec 4, 1986; cuid5953 (Box 66, Cassette 68)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Dec 11, 1986; cuid5954 (Box 66, Cassette 69)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Dec 18, 1986; cuid5955 (Box 66, Cassette 70)
    - Work With the Homeless, Jan 8, 1987; cuid5956 (Box 66, Cassette 71)
    - The Homeless, Jan 15, 1987; cuid5957 (Box 66, Cassette 72)
    - Talking Union (with Frank Morelli and Stanley Hill), Jan 28, 1987; cuid5958 (Box 66, Cassette 73)
    - Talking Union (with Frank Morelli and Stanley Hill), Jan 29, 1987; cuid5959 (Box 66, Cassette 74)
    - Black History Program, Feb 12, 1987; cuid5960 (Box 66, Cassette 75)
    - Black History Month, Feb 26, 1987; cuid5961 (Box 66, Cassette 76)
    - Women at Work, Mar 5, 1987; cuid5962 (Box 66, Cassette 77-78)
    - Gardening, Apr 2, 1987; cuid5963 (Box 66, Cassette 79)
    - March on Washington, Apr 9, 1987; cuid5964 (Box 66, Cassette 80)
    - The Bronx Zoo, Apr 23, 1987; cuid5965 (Box 66, Cassette 81)
    - New York City Recreation, May 7, 1987; cuid5966 (Box 66, Cassette 82)
    - Labor History, May 21, 1987; cuid5967 (Box 66, Cassette 83)
    - Occupational Health and Safety Administration (OSHA), Jun 4, 1987; cuid5968 (Box 66, Cassette 84-85)
    - Summer in the City, Jun 25, 1987; cuid5969 (Box 66, Cassette 86-87)
    - New Announcer Introduction, Promo, and Closing, Oct 5, 1987; cuid5970 (Box 66, Cassette 88)
    - 911 Technicians, Oct 11, 1987; cuid5971 (Box 66, Cassette 89)
    - Emergency Medical Services, Oct 25, 1987; cuid5972 (Box 66, Cassette 90-91)
    - Music (You Can Be Happy, Celestial Choir), Oct 25, 1987; cuid5973 (Box 66, Cassette 92)
    - Puerto Rican Heritage, Nov 11, 1987; cuid5974 (Box 66, Cassette 93)
    - Whistleblowers, Nov 22, 1987; cuid5975 (Box 66, Cassette 94)
    - Domestic Violence, Dec 6 ,1987; cuid5976 (Box 66, Cassette 95)
    - Domestic Violence, Jan 17, 1988; cuid5977 (Box 66, Cassette 96)
    - Public Health System Nurses, Jan 31, 1988; cuid5978 (Box 66, Cassette 97)
    - Black History Month, Feb 3, 1988; cuid5979 (Box 66, Cassette 98)
    - Hughes, Charles and Stanley Hill, Feb 18, 1988; cuid5980 (Box 66, Cassette 99)
    - Eldridge, Ron and Cream Tea, Feb 19, 1988; cuid5981 (Box 66, Cassette 100)
    - Ibrahim, Abdullah (Local 371), Feb 19, 1988; cuid5982 (Box 66, Cassette 101)
    - Black History, Feb 28, 1988; cuid5983 (Box 66, Cassette 102)
    - Women's History, Mar 30, 1988; cuid5984 (Box 66, Cassette 103)
    - Public Libraries, Apr 10, 1988; cuid5985 (Box 66, Cassette 104)
    - New York Museums, May 8, 1988; cuid5986 (Box 66, Cassette 105)
    - Tax Assessors, May 15, 1988; cuid5987 (Box 66, Cassette 106)
    - New York Bridges, May 29, 1988; cuid5988 (Box 66, Cassette 107)
    - The Other Island, Jun 12, 1988; cuid5989 (Box 66, Cassette 108)
    - Presidential Election (Oct 18, 1988)/Sewage Treatment Workers (Nov 1, 1988), cuid5990 (Box 66, Cassette 109)
    - People's Court (Nov 29, 1988)/Holiday Headaches (1988), cuid5991 (Box 66, Cassette 110)
    - Holiday Show, Dec 7, 1988; cuid5992 (Box 66, Cassette 111)
    - Come to the Cabaret (Dec 13, 1988)/People Helping People (Jan 10, 1989), 1988-1989; cuid5993 (Box 66, Cassette 112)
    - Hospitals in Crisis, Jan 31, 1989; cuid5994 (Box 66, Cassette 113)
    - Hospitals in Crisis (Jan 31, 1989)/Black History (Feb 14, 1989), Jan-Feb, 1989; cuid5995 (Box 66, Cassette 114)
    - Shop Stewards (Mar 7, 1989)/Women's Work (Mar 21, 1989), Mar 1989; cuid5996 (Box 66, Cassette 115, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_115)
    - City Infrastructure (Apr 4, 1989)/PSU Outreach Program (Apr 18, 1989), Apr 1989; cuid5997 (Box 66, Cassette 116)
    - Today's Technology, Tomorrow's Health (May 2, 1989)/CUNY Crisis (May 16, 1989), May 1989; cuid5998 (Box 66, Cassette 117)
    - Active Retirees (May 30, 1989)/Off-Track Betting (OTB) Employees (Jun 13, 1989), May-Jun 1989; cuid5999 (Box 66, Cassette 118)
    - Central Park Zoo (Jun 27, 1989)/Kids, Crime, Counselors (Jul 11, 1989), Jun-Jul 1989; cuid6000 (Box 66, Cassette 119)
    - Health Care Funding, Oct 17, 1989; cuid6001 (Box 66, Cassette 120-121)
    - Public Services International (PSI) Report, Dec 5, 1989; cuid6002 (Box 66, Cassette 122)
    - Come to the Cabaret, Dec 13, 1989; cuid6003 (Box 66, Cassette 123)
    - Reading Comprehension (Jan 30, 1991)/Educational Fund (N.D.), cuid6004 (Box 66, Cassette 124)
    - Educational Fund-Supervisory Skills for APP Test Preparation Series, Feb 27, 1991; cuid6005 (Box 66, Cassette 125)
    - Rally Special, Sep 3, 1991; cuid6006 (Box 66, Cassette 126)
    - Black History Month, Feb 10, 1992; cuid6007 (Box 66, Cassette 127)
    - Hispanic Heritage--Jose Labor, 1994 August 30; cuid6008 (Box 67, Cassette 150, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_256)
    - Harlem-New City, Oct 17, 1994; cuid6009 (Box 66, Cassette 128)
    - Contract on America, Jan 1995; cuid6010 (Box 66, Cassette 129-130)
    - Post-Holiday Bills Blues, Jan 20, 1995; cuid6011 (Box 67, Cassette 131)
    - Unidentified Program, Jan 27, 1995; cuid6012 (Box 67, Cassette 132, Box 76, Audiocassette 132)
    - Black History Month, Mar 3, 1995; cuid6013 (Box 67, Cassette 133, Box 76, Audiocassette 133)
    - Retiree's Association, May 1995; cuid6014 (Box 67, Cassette 134, Box 76, Audiocassette 134)
    - Community and Labor Coalitions, Jun 23, 1995; cuid6015 (Box 67, Cassette 135, Box 76, Audiocassette 135)
    - Hispanic Heritage, Oct 19, 1995; cuid6016 (Box 67, Cassette 136, Box 76, Audiocassette 136)
    - Celebrating Women's Month, Apr 12, 1996; cuid6017 (Box 67, Cassette 137, Box 76, Audiocassette 137)
    - [Unidentified Program], May 17, 1996; cuid6018 (Box 67, Cassette 138, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_138)
    - Domestic Violence, Jun 7, 1996; cuid6019 (Box 67, Cassette 139, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_139)
    - Economics at DC 37, Oct 23, 1996; cuid6020 (Box 67, Cassette 140, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_140)
    - Black History: Tuskegee Airmen, Feb 5, 1997; cuid6021 (Box 67, Cassette 141, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_141)
    - Black History: Tuskegee Airmen [DAT Cassette], Feb 5, 1997; cuid6022 (Box 67, Cassette 142, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_142)
    - [Unidentified Interview DAT Cassette], Sep 8, 1997; cuid6023 (Box 67, Cassette 143, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_143)
    - Hidden Disabilities Interview, Sep 18, 1997; cuid6024 (Box 67, Cassette 144, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_144)
    - AFL-CIO Convention, Sep 31, 1997; cuid6025 (Box 67, Cassette 145, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_145)
    - Black History Celebration, Feb 27, 1998; cuid6026 (Box 67, Cassette 146-147, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_146, 265_147)
  - Subseries VIII:B: Other Radio Shows Audio Cassettes, 1979-1997.
    - "Building Bridges": Gay and Lesbian Issues, Undated; cuid6027 (Box 67, Cassette 148, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_148)
    - "Building Bridges": Local 1930 Rally, Undated; cuid6028 (Box 67, Cassette 149, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_149)
    - "Public Employee": Gus Tyler and Victor Gotbaum, Undated; cuid6029 (Box 67, Cassette 150, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_150)
    - "Political Action" (DC 37), Jun 20, 1979; cuid6030 (Box 67, Cassette 151, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_151)
    - "Good Times, Bad Times": Local 372, 1982; cuid6031 (Box 67, Cassette 152, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_152)
    - "Newsbeat": Are Unions in Trouble? (with Victor Gotbaum), 1984; cuid6032 (Box 67, Cassette 153, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_153)
    - "Building Bridges": Teamsters Local 810 Strikers, Jun 4, 1987; cuid6033 (Box 67, Cassette 154, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_154)
    - "English Language Skills" (DC 37 Educational Fund), Feb 6, 1991; cuid6034 (Box 67, Cassette 155, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_155)
    - "Building Bridges": Morris Dees (Southern Poverty Law Center), Gathering Storm: America's Militia Threat, May 13, 1996; cuid6035 (Box 67, Cassette 156, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_156)
    - Educational Fund and Women's Council Program, Mar 31, 1997; cuid6036 (Box 67, Cassette 157, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_157)
    - HRA Commissioner/Jason Turner, Jun 30, 1998; cuid6037 (Box 67, Cassette 248, Box Shared Tamiment 168, Audiocassette 265_248)
    - Interview with Eric Lars Nelson of Newsday, Oct 5, 1998; cuid6038 (Box 67, Cassette 249, Box Shared Tamiment 168, Audiocassette 265_249)
    - Tom Defrank, Oct 8, 1998; cuid6039 (Box 67, Cassette 250, Box Shared Tamiment 168, Audiocassette 265_250)
    - Nita Lowey, Oct 8, 1998; cuid6040 (Box 67, Cassette 251, Box Shared Tamiment 168, Audiocassette 265_251)
    - Foster Care, Oct 21, 1998; cuid6041 (Box 67, Cassette 252)
    - Newsday/Marie Coco, Oct 30, 1998; cuid6042 (Box 67, Cassette 253, Box Shared Tamiment 168, Audiocassette 265_253)
    - Dennis Duggan/Lanny Sanjek, Nov 16, 1998; cuid6043 (Box 67, Cassette 254)
  - Subseries VIII:C: Radio Spots Audio Cassettes, 1979-1987.
    - City Council Committee on Aging Hearings, Report, Undated; cuid6044 (Box 67, Cassette 158, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_158)
    - Meeting Union Members, Mar 1, 1979; cuid6045 (Box 67, Cassette 159, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_159)
    - City Workers Advise Public About City Services (6 Spots), May 17, 1984; cuid6046 (Box 67, Cassette 160, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_160)
    - City Workers Advise Public About City Services (11 Spots), Jun 5, 1984; cuid6047 (Box 67, Cassette 161, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_161)
    - Hall, Sonny and Victor Gotbaum on MTA Contract Negotiations, 1986; cuid6048 (Box 67, Cassette 162, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_162)
    - Employees for Improved Transit (3 Spots), 1986; cuid6049 (Box 67, Cassette 163, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_163)
    - DC 37 Contract Negotiations (4 Spots), 1987; cuid6050 (Box 67, Cassette 164-167, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_164, 265_165, 265_166, 265_167)
  - Subseries VIII:D: Interviews and Speeches Audio Cassettes, 1979-1999.
    - Bernstein, Rachel and Gail Malmgreen Interview on Debra Bernhardt, Mar 2001; cuid6051 (Box 67, Cassette 167a, Box 76, Audiocassette 265_167A)
    - Castillo, Luisa Amelia, Marian Porro, and Lynn Taylor Interview, Undated; cuid6052 (Box 67, Cassette 168, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_168)
    - Claxton, Anna (Local 372) Speech, Jul 25, 1979; cuid6053 (Box 67, Cassette 169, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_169)
    - Clinton, Bill Speech to Trade Unionists, Undated; cuid6054 (Box 67, Cassette 170, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_170)
    - Gotbaum, Victor Speech on Mayor John Lindsay, Undated; cuid6055 (Box 67, Cassette 171, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_171)
    - Gotbaum, Victor Speech to DC 37 Delegates, Jan 29, 1987; cuid6056 (Box 67, Cassette 172, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_172)
    - Hill, Stanley and Ralph Neas Interview, Jan 19, 1987; cuid6057 (Box 67, Cassette 173, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_173)
    - Hill, Stanley Interview on Contract Negotiations, Oct 18, 1990; cuid6058 (Box 67, Cassette 174, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_174)
    - Hill, Stanley Speech: "Just Like You", Undated; cuid6059 (Box 67, Cassette 175)
    - Hill, Stanley Speech at Local 372 Black History Month Celebration, Feb 20, 1998; cuid6060 (Box 67, Cassette 176, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_176)
    - Howard, Al Interview on Corruption in City Government, Undated; cuid6061 (Box 67, Cassette 177, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_177)
    - Hughes, Charles and Victor Gotbaum Speeches to Local 372, Mar 8, 1982; cuid6062 (Box 67, Cassette 178, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_178)
    - Jackson, Jesse Speech at UAW Rally, Feb 23, 1988; cuid6063 (Box 67, Cassette 179, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_179)
    - Kerstein, Goodie and Catherine Bruno Interview (Local 372), Jul 19, 1979; cuid6064 (Box 67, Cassette 180, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_180)
    - Labor Day Parades Interviews, Undated; cuid6065 (Box 67, Cassette 181, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_181)
    - Library Guild Leaders Interviews at Rally (Local 1930), Oct 21, 1999; cuid6066 (Box 67, Cassette 182, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_182)
    - Mackey, [Nathaniel?] Interview on "Black Language", Undated; cuid6067 (Box 67, Cassette 183, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_183)
    - Mandela, Nelson Speech at Unknown AFSCME Conference, Undated; cuid6068 (Box 67, Cassette 184, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_184)
    - Richards, Ann Speech, San Diego, Undated; cuid6069 (Box 67, Cassette 185, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_185)
    - Roberts, Lillian Speech at Rally (introduction by James Butler), Undated; cuid6070 (Box 67, Cassette 186, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_186)
    - Unidentified Participants Interview on UFT Contract, Undated; cuid6071 (Box 67, Cassette 187, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_187)
    - Unidentified Participants Interview on Unidentified Subject, Undated; cuid6072 (Box 67, Cassette 188)
    - Wildavsky, Aaron Interview (author of Speaking Truth to Power), Mar 19, 1981; cuid6073 (Box 67, Cassette 189)
  - Subseries VIII:E: Conferences and Conventions Audio Cassettes, 1983-1997.
    - AFL-CIO Organizing Conference, Apr 29, 1997; cuid6074 (Box 67, Cassette 190, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_190)
    - AFSCME Conference: "Welfare Reform for Work and Dignity" (tape 1 of 2), Dec 3, 1996; cuid6075 (Box 67, Cassette 191, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_191)
    - AFSCME Conference: "Welfare Reform for Work and Dignity" (tape 2 of 2), Dec 3, 1996; cuid6076 (Box 67, Cassette 192, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_192)
    - AFSCME 30th Annual International Convention, Las Vegas (tape 1 of 3), 1992; cuid6077 (Box 67, Cassette 193, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_193)
    - AFSCME 30th Annual International Convention, Las Vegas (tape 2 of 3), 1992; cuid6078 (Box 67, Cassette 194)
    - AFSCME 30th Annual International Convention, Las Vegas (tape 3 of 3), 1992; cuid6079 (Box 67, Cassette 195)
    - AFSCME Convention Speech by Bill Lucy, 1996; cuid6080 (Box 67, Cassette 196, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_196)
    - DC 37 Conference: "Changing Situation", 1985; cuid6081 (Box 67, Cassette 197)
    - DC 37 Conference: "Changing Situation" Workshop, "New Forms and Structures", 1985; cuid6082 (Box 67, Cassette 198)
    - DC 37 Conference: "Changing Situation" Workshop on Public Opinion and Public Relations (tape 1 of 2), 1985; cuid6083 (Box 67, Cassette 199, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_199)
    - DC 37 Conference: "Changing Situation" Workshop on Public Opinion and Public Relations (tape 2 of 2), 1985; cuid6084 (Box 67, Cassette 200, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_200)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Introduction [DAT Cassette], Jun 22, 1991; cuid6085 (Box 67, Cassette 201, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_201)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Gerald McEntee [DAT Cassette], Jun 22, 1991; cuid6086 (Box 67, Cassette 202, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_202)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Stanley Hill Closing Speech, Jul 14, 1987; cuid6087 (Box 67, Cassette 203, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_203)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Stanley Hill Speech, Jul 14, 1987; cuid6088 (Box 67, Cassette 204, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_204)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Stanley Hill Speech [DAT Cassette], 1995; cuid6089 (Box 67, Cassette 205)
    - DC 37 Professional Division Conference: Roundtable Discussion (tape 1 of 2), 1985; cuid6090 (Box 67, Cassette 206)
    - DC 37 Professional Division Conference: Roundtable Discussion (tape 2 of 2), 1985; cuid6091 (Box 67, Cassette 207)
    - Hospitals Conference (tape 1 of 2), May 2, 1987; cuid6092 (Box 67, Cassette 208, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_208)
    - Hospitals Conference (tape 2 of 2), May 2, 1987; cuid6093 (Box 67, Cassette 209, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_209)
    - Lesbian and Gay East Coast Conference (tape 1 of 2), Undated; cuid6094 (Box 67, Cassette 210)
    - Lesbian and Gay East Coast Conference (tape 2 of 2), Undated; cuid6095 (Box 67, Cassette 211)
    - Local 436 Conference: "Mainstreaming Handicapped", 1983; cuid6096 (Box 67, Cassette 212, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_212)
    - Local 436 Conference: "Mainstreaming Handicapped" Speech by Annie [?], 1983; cuid6097 (Box 67, Cassette 213, Box 77, Audiocassette 265_213)
    - Unknown Conference: Speech by Bill Lucy, Undated; cuid6098 (Box 67, Cassette 214)